Nazar Kublii

PYTHON BACKEND-DEVELOPER



Summary

I have always loved and admired complex things, so coding has become my main hobby. I was used to complex tasks, finding solutions quickly, and learning. At the age of 13, I became interested in programming. In 2017 I entered an IT academy and at the end of my studies, I participated in an educational project on C#.NetFramework. After that, I did freelance orders on Python, Kotlin, and Lua. I also have experience programming in C, C++, Java, SQL

EXPERIENCE

PYTHON JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Freelance | 2017 - 2021

- A utility for managing user funds of crypto-exchange platforms (Binance, bitfinex) through the provided API(Python, GUI PyQt)
- A utility for sending congratulatory letters to the clients of the place via Telegram messenger. (Python, telethon, sqlite, openpyxl)
- Telegram bot + Android application (Python, sqlite, openpyxl, flask-RESTful, telethon, python-telegram-bot) + (Kotlin, android API 28)
- Scrapy parser for eBay platform. (Python, Scrapy)

Own business | 2021 - 2022

- Flask web application for managing local documents and credentials. (Python, Flask, sqlAlchemy, sqlite, Jinja2, JS, Bootstrap.
- On Django rewritten the previous web app.

Pet project | 2021 - 2022

 FastAPI-based simple messenger API. (Python, FastApi, sqlAlchemy, PostgreSQL, Pydantic, Alembic, Celery).

SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

CallCenter | Feb 2020 - Dec 2020 Computer club | July 2019 - december 2019

Laying network cable and service internal network, equipment maintain.

EDUCATION

ADDITIONAL EDUCATION

IT- ACADEMY Algorithmization and programming 2017-2018

- C, C++, Java, C#
- Algorithmization
- Discrete math

VTEI "VIHVS"

Computer typing operator. Electromechanic for the repair and maintenance of computers 2012 - 2015

Profile

24 y.o. (24.12.1997) Vinnytsya

Objective

I want to realize my potential as python developer and engineer, to get experience in corporate environment, improve tech skills, develop soft skills

Hard Skills

Main language:

Python 3 (FastAPI, sqlAlchemy, pydantic, Flask, Flask-RESTful, Flask-SQLAlchemy, Django, Django REST, Jinja2, BeautifulSoup4, unittest)

Base syntax:

C, C++, C#, Java, Kotlin, Lua, HTML, JS

Version control: Git

Other skills:

Linux, Bash, Docker, MySQL, PostgreSQL

English: Intermediate (A2-B1)

Soft Skills

- Stress-tolerant in dynamical environment
- Detail-oriented
- Critical thinking

Contacts

email: n.kubliy@gmail.com

github: https://github.com/NazikXY

tel.: +380638294413

linkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/nkubliy/